JEREMY BUKOFZER

Milwaukee, WI Phone: 918-521-8991 Email: jlbukofzer@gmail.com

CAREER GOAL

To find a position where I can utilize my problem-solving skills, as well as lead and be a part of a team where I can develop my leadership skills. Also, I would like to have the ability to share my best practices, knowledge, and experience with others as a part of a cohesive team

WORK EXPERIENCE

Whole Foods Market Specialty Cheese Buyer

Wauwatosa, WI Apr 2021-Present

Duties: Assist customers in their beer, wine, cheese, and coffee inquiries while providing excellent customer service. Maintain a safe and clean workspace. Clean, cut, wrap, and display cheese.

Whole Foods Market Specialty Team Member

Bellevue, WA-Wauwatosa, WI 2017-2021

Duties: Assist customers in their beer, wine, cheese, and coffee inquiries while providing excellent customer service. Maintain a safe and clean workspace. Clean, cut, wrap, and display cheese.

Parker Staffing at Nintendo of America Contact Center Associate (contract)

Redmond, WA 2017

Duties: Assist consumers with technical, network, account inquiries pertaining to the Nintendo gaming consoles and software. Handle incidents with efficiency, while providing excellent customer service. Ensuring consumers needs meet the needs of the company.

DISH Network Customer Service Representative

Tulsa, OK

2016

Duties: Assisting customers with technical, billing and programing inquiries. Staying up to date on the technology within the pay-tv industry.

GameStop Senior Game Advisor (Shift-Leader)

Tulsa, OK

2015-2016

Duties: Assist customers with questions about video games, as well as up-sell customers. Lead other game advisors in daily duties. Deal with managerial tasks and issues.

DIRECTV Assistance Queue Specialist/Team Lead

Tulsa, OK

2014-2015

Duties: Train and mentor a team of CSR's to ensure customers receive the best quality of service. Schedule one-on-ones with representatives to enhance individual performance. Handle escalated customers to find common ground to ensure customer satisfaction. Build relationships and trust with customers to diffuse negative situations. Manage a team of tech CSR's to ensure their success.

Jeremy Bukofzer Page 2

Michaels Tulsa, OK Framing Expert 2013-2014

Duties: Training new employees and assigning projects to other framers. Designing, and constructing frames and matting for artwork. Assist customers in designing a proper frame and mat combination to best compliment their artwork.

Pizza HutTulsa, OKDelivery Driver2011-2012

Duties: Assigning delivery routes to other drivers, training new drivers, while delivering and preparing pizzas. Employee of the month for September 2011.

Best Buy Tulsa, OK Media Specialist/Merchandising Specialist 2007-2010

Duties: Ensure shelves are properly stocked, and order merchandise when necessary. Update sale signs and prices of product. Build displays of product. Unload trucks as part of a team while assigning co-workers to designated departments, and assuring the product was properly distributed.

EDUCATION

Tulsa Community College

Tulsa, OK

Working towards a degree in art and illustration to become a concept artist, and studying for A+ and Network+ certifications.

Tulsa Technology Center

Tulsa, OK

Studied in the design aspect of web design using Photoshop, Illustrator, and Flash, as well as the programming side of web development.

TRAINING/CERTIFICAIONS

DIRECTV Career Development Program: Learned ways to network within a company, and understand the day-to-day life throughout the DIRECTV call center. Developed skills to organize and plan a career path by setting time-bound and obtainable objectives.

Whole Foods CCATL: Learned how to lead a team while meeting business needs.